Tran Ngoc Hung

Vietnam



trhung26620@gmail.com



+84789978995



linkedin.com/in/hung-tran-0829a1209



https://trhung26620.github.io/

Summary

I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Information Assurance in 2022. However, I started working for a company providing cyber security services in 2021 with the job of Web/App Penetrating Testing. For nearly 2 years, my main job is as a security researcher, programming vulnerability testing tools, finding and exploiting vulnerabilities for Websites/Applications related to the fields: banking, finance, insurance,...

Recently, when I had the opportunity to learn about blockchain, I was extremely interested in the strengths of this technology, so I decided to learn and develop Web3 projects. Regarding my future plans, I want to be an expert in the blockchain field in the next 3 years.

Experience



Blockchain Developer

Self-Study

Sep 2022 - Present (6 months)

Self-study on Web3, Blockchain, Dapps and develop personal projects such as: NFT Marketplace, Booking Care Dapp, Charity DAO App



Web/App Pentester

Techlab Corporation

May 2021 - Jan 2023 (1 year 9 months)

- Develop tools for penetration testing
- Find and exploit security vulnerabilities of websites, Android/IOS applications -
- Build security checklist (Database and programming language) for developers

Education

FPT University

Bachelor's Degree, Information Assurance

2018 - 2022

High achievements in subjects such as Programming C, Java, Java OOP, Desktop Java Application, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, Database Systems, Data Structures and Algorithms, Networking, Web Security, Database Security

Skills

React.js • Node.js • Express.js • Cryptography • Solidity • Cybersecurity • Blockchain • JavaScript • Python (Programming Language) • Decentralized Applications (DApps)